- [Instructor] With your new knowledge,
you should be able to easily and quickly build
a full stack application with MERN
and apply it to almost any type of applications.
To explore this further,
you could simply replicate the same process we've done
by creating other collections, models
and schemas for your database,
and also create the new endpoints for the front end to call.
Also, if you'd like to keep exploring what you can do
with React, there are tons of courses
related to this front end framework.
Also, if you'd like to build mobile application
as your front end, you can explore React Native
as your next option.
Finally, if you prefer, you'd like to learn
a bit more about how to use Mongo
and what advanced queries are available with this database,
look for courses on this subject in our library.
Thanks very much for taking my course,
and I'll see you in a bit.